<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Pandu Akhbar</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Pandu Akhbar</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.123.7</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 04:57:18 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>my dearest alisha, my sweetest lily</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/lily/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 04:57:18 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/lily/</guid>
      <description>I hope today you stopped to feel the wind on your skin. I hope you paused, even for a moment—to feel the sunlight, to take a breath between chapters of the rush of your days. I hope you know that even in the midst of chaos, the world holds moments meant only for you. I love you. Though we live in places so far apart that even the seasons seem out of sync, I still feel you close to me.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 04:57:18 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Introduction HIII Halooo HIII haloo test</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/aboutme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/aboutme/</guid>
      <description>“I saw my life branching out before me like the green fig tree in the story. From the tip of every branch, like a fat purple fig, a wonderful future beckoned and winked. One fig was a husband and a happy home and children, and another fig was a famous poet and another fig was a brilliant professor, and another fig was Ee Gee, the amazing editor, and another fig was Europe and Africa and South America, and another fig was Constantin and Socrates and Attila and a pack of other lovers with queer names and offbeat professions, and another fig was an Olympic lady crew champion, and beyond and above these figs were many more figs I couldn&amp;rsquo;t quite make out.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
